Search Menu

Secondary Menu Search

Go

[

](https://thebackroomtech.com/ "The Back Room Tech")

Privacy Policy
==============

Written by: [Aseem Kishore](https://thebackroomtech.com/author/akishoretbrt/)  
Posted on: August 20th, 2018 in:

**Privacy Policy for TheBackRoomTech.com**

The privacy of our visitors to TheBackRoomTech.com is very important to us.

At TheBackRoomTech.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit TheBackRoomTech.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Ezoic Ads**

**Log Files  
**  
In accordance with the Adsense Terms of Service, we are required to let you know that all advertising programs use cookies to track visitors. As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as Cox or AT&T), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons  
**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on TheBackRoomTech.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing ads based on location or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively [turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings](https://www.online-tech-tips.com/computer-tips/delete-cookies/), or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Email Addresses**

When you make a comment or contact me using the contact page you email is required. Please be assured that you email address will only be used for responding to your email or comment and will never be made publicly available. We will never sell your email address to any third parties, ever.

**Comments Policy**

The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectionable and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster banned!

Spam in any form will not be accepted.

**Copyrights**

Supreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please [contact me](https://thebackroomtech.com/contact/) immediately.

#### Daily Email Newsletter

#### Recent Posts

* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2023/02/15/top-10-command-line-tools-every-linux-administrator-should-know/ "Top 10 Command-Line Tools Every Linux Administrator Should Know")[Top 10 Command-Line Tools Every Linux Administrator Should Know](https://thebackroomtech.com/2023/02/15/top-10-command-line-tools-every-linux-administrator-should-know/ "Top 10 Command-Line Tools Every Linux Administrator Should Know")
* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2023/02/14/cmdlets-101-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them-in-powershell/ "Cmdlets 101: What They Are and How to Use Them in PowerShell")[Cmdlets 101: What They Are and How to Use Them in PowerShell](https://thebackroomtech.com/2023/02/14/cmdlets-101-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them-in-powershell/ "Cmdlets 101: What They Are and How to Use Them in PowerShell")
* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2021/03/22/how-to-install-ftp-server-on-windows-server-2019/ "How to Install FTP Server on Windows Server 2019")[How to Install FTP Server on Windows Server 2019](https://thebackroomtech.com/2021/03/22/how-to-install-ftp-server-on-windows-server-2019/ "How to Install FTP Server on Windows Server 2019")
* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2021/03/19/how-to-install-and-run-flatpak-applications/ "How to Install and Run Flatpak Applications")[How to Install and Run Flatpak Applications](https://thebackroomtech.com/2021/03/19/how-to-install-and-run-flatpak-applications/ "How to Install and Run Flatpak Applications")

#### Random Posts

* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2008/06/05/howto-export-3com-4xxx-family-switch-configurations-to-a-text-file-for-backup-and-change-management/ "How to Export 3com 4xxx Family Switch Configurations to a Text File for Backup and Change Management")[How to Export 3com 4xxx Family Switch Configurations to a Text File for Backup and Change Management](https://thebackroomtech.com/2008/06/05/howto-export-3com-4xxx-family-switch-configurations-to-a-text-file-for-backup-and-change-management/ "How to Export 3com 4xxx Family Switch Configurations to a Text File for Backup and Change Management")
* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2007/11/20/resources-for-troubleshooting-windows-event-2019-the-server-was-unable-to-allocate-from-the-system-nonpaged-pool-because-the-pool-was-empty/ "Resources for Troubleshooting Windows Event 2019: The server was unable to allocate from the system nonpaged pool because the pool was empty")[Resources for Troubleshooting Windows Event 2019: The server was unable to allocate from the system nonpaged pool because the pool was empty](https://thebackroomtech.com/2007/11/20/resources-for-troubleshooting-windows-event-2019-the-server-was-unable-to-allocate-from-the-system-nonpaged-pool-because-the-pool-was-empty/ "Resources for Troubleshooting Windows Event 2019: The server was unable to allocate from the system nonpaged pool because the pool was empty")
* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2023/02/14/cmdlets-101-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them-in-powershell/ "Cmdlets 101: What They Are and How to Use Them in PowerShell")[Cmdlets 101: What They Are and How to Use Them in PowerShell](https://thebackroomtech.com/2023/02/14/cmdlets-101-what-they-are-and-how-to-use-them-in-powershell/ "Cmdlets 101: What They Are and How to Use Them in PowerShell")
* [
    
    ](https://thebackroomtech.com/2018/04/17/installing-and-configuring-active-directory-domain-services-on-windows-server-2016/ "Installing and Configuring Active Directory Domain Services on Windows Server 2016")[Installing and Configuring Active Directory Domain Services on Windows Server 2016](https://thebackroomtech.com/2018/04/17/installing-and-configuring-active-directory-domain-services-on-windows-server-2016/ "Installing and Configuring Active Directory Domain Services on Windows Server 2016")

#### Our Publishing Family

The Back Room Tech is part of the AK Internet Consulting publishing family.

#### Daily Email Newsletter

#### CONNECT WITH US

#### About The Back Room Tech

Welcome to The Back Room Tech- a tech blog for those who work in server back rooms. My name is Aseem Kishore and I am a full-time professional blogger. I graduated from Emory University with a degree in Computer Science and Mathematics.

Copyright © 2010-2024 The Back Room Tech.com, LLC All Rights Reserved
